us with your thoughts on the magnitude of SDI improvement you're hoping to show, and
indeed, whether you still consider that to be the right and definitive endpoint.
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks, Emmanuel.
So, absolutely, we saw very fast enrollment, faster than expected enrollment for inalimum
in Sjogren's.
We have pulled forward that readout.
As you know, Sjogren's, again, a relatively prevalent rheumatological disease without
really any great, good treatment options.
The Phase II data for inalimum out of Sjogren's showed, you know, really the first time that
you could have a significant improvement in SDI as well as other patient report outcomes.
So, obviously, we won't quantitate the magnitudes of SDI benefit, but if we can repeat what
we saw in Phase IIb, we think that would be really a compelling option.
Also, a unique mechanism of action, anti-bath, allows you to deplete B cells in multiple
components.
Which we think will be important for a disease like Sjogren's, which impacts multiple different
tissues.
I think what will be important in addition to SDI is patient reported outcomes, meaning
salivary gland function, dry eye.
Many of these things, these areas are what patients would like to see improved.
And if we can demonstrate, in addition to the composite endpoint, PROs that show important
benefits for these patients, we think this could be an exciting opportunity.
Overall, we're looking at a lot of different things.
Overall, we think Ionilumab is a multi-billion dollar opportunity in combination with Sjogren's.
We have multiple other Phase III programs ongoing and four separate hematological indications
where we expect readouts in 2027.
We also take Ionilumab into other immunology indications as well.
So, this is an opportunity for us to really build a significant medicine.
And as a reminder as well, this medicine has protection into the mid to late 2030s.
Thank you.
Next question, operator.
Your next question comes from the line of Richard Parks from BNP Paribas.
Please go ahead.
Hi, thank you for taking my question.
I was going to stick on pipeline events in 2025.
On Pelicast, I don't know, probably your next sort of multi-bot was to read out.
Could you just remind us what your powering assumptions are in terms of the benefit that
you're looking to see in the LP little a horizon trial?
And then can you talk about balance?
So, barriers to uptake of LP little a targeting agents, obviously, PCSK9 uptake's been disappointing
for investors, partly attributed to the need for injections and costs.
I'm just wondering if those barriers are going to also limit LP little a targeting agents,
or is the lack of available alternatives for patients with elevated LP little a going
to mean those barriers are less significant?
So, if you could just talk about that, that would be great.
Thank you.
Thank you, Richard.
So, first, in terms of the study design, the way we designed the Pelicast study was to
look at two different levels of LP little a.
So, first, the top quartile of, at the top quartile of LP little a levels, and then
a separate analysis, still part of the primary endpoint, which allows us to take a second
look at the top decile of patients in terms of their level of LP little a.
And that was based on, you know, large-scale epidemiologic studies on how to, you know,
how risk evolves from different quartiles and deciles of patients with elevated LP little a.
So, our hope is to show us both of those analysis, and our goal will be to show greater than 20% CVRR.
But, of course, we have aspirations to get even higher.
And I think if we can show even higher levels, that would certainly create a lot of motivation
in physicians to make sure these patients are tested.
One of the things we've learned, I think, through our various cardiovascular launches is,
in this day and age, to take more of a specialty cardiology mindset in how we think about
launching these medicines.
So, rather than trying to do broad-based LP little a testing for patients across large
populations, to actually look very systematically, looking at large-scale data sets, and really
targeting the groups, ethnicities that have the highest risk of elevated LP little a,
and try to promote high levels of testing within those patient populations.
And alongside that, to target specialty groups, which have a higher propensity to want to
test and treat.
So, those are, of course, cardiovascular specialty groups, but also, when you think about interventional
cardiology, I mean, there are certain specialty groups we're learning that have a higher propensity
to look for these biomarkers and then treat in order to avoid the recurrence of events,
also given the push towards healthcare quality around the world.
So, we're trying to take a broad-based approach.
We're trying to take a very targeted approach in how we